

# Asmat Ali Full stack Developer

# My Contact

□ asmat6894@gmail.com

**(**) +923439602946

Mingora Swat Pakistan

https://asmataligran.github.io/asmat/

#### **Skills**

- project Management
- Html ,Css,Bootstrap
- javaScript,jQuery,Ajax
- PHP,laravel, Vue.js
- Rest Api's
- · designing
- · Teaching
- Communication
- Multi-tasking
- Computer operator

#### **Educations**

- khpalKor model school & collage pre-engineering
   Completed in 2018
- Collage of modren science
   Diploma information Technology (DIT)
   Completed in 2017
- Virtual University Of Pakistan
   Bachelor of computer science (BS)

   Completed in 2022

## **LANGUAGES**

pashto, Urdu ,English

# Certificate

police driving license school Presentation 1st position

#### **About Me**

Hey I'm Asmat, a developer with 2+ years experience writing HTML,Css,Bootstrap,javascript,jquery, PHP,Sql laravel & vue.js.

I specialize in building web apps using frameworks like Laravel, and Vue.js.

I work remotely with teams to build appropriate, elegant and reliable solutions to complex problems – helping global companies,

## **Professional Experience**

Zarnain Graphic Designing 2019 – 2020

Key responsibilities:

- Make designing for shop and Hospital & ect
- printing press design and brochure design
- school Paper and documents, Urdu Writing

Webdsoft Company Limit| full stack/Internship

2020 - 2021

Key responsibilities:

- Develop responsive websites using HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, jQuery/JavaScript Php
- complete Online Charity Management (final year Project) php
- Complete Shop project (mohib designing shop) php

Said Information technology| Full Stack Developer 2021 – present

- Key responsibilities:
- Make Web Application & Mobile Application
- Tools Use [HTM , Css, Bootstrap, jquery, Laravel ,Api ,Git,Adob Xd]

Complete Project| Full Stack Developer (Top 10) Project

- Enaba Almanasek [full stack] https://enabatalmanasek.com/
- Education (Laravel, Reacts) [backend developer] https://baseerat.saidapp.work/
- Hotel (Management) App [full stack ] https://nadel.sa/ [backend developer ]
- company website (Laravel) [full stack] https://sharpvisions.sa/
- portfolio(Laravel) [full stack] https://mshahzeb.com/
- Ecommerce (Laravel) [full stack]
   https://movl.mostatel.com/
- Website (Bootstrap) [Bootstrap developer] http://expaninno.orangespark.net/
- Software House Website (Bootstrap) [Bootstrap developer]
   https://orangespark.net/(Bootstrap)
- Ecommerce (Laravel) [full stack]
  https://soul-boutiques.com/